Guide to The Packer Collegiate Institute records 2014.019
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 17: Photographs, 1845-circa 2010; 58 Cubic Feet
  - Sub-series 17.1: Packer Collegiate Institute photographs, circa 1850-circa 2010; 50 Cubic Feet in 107 boxes
    - Playground Construction 18, 1993-1994 (Box 289, Folder 13)
    - Graduation, 1993-1996 (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - International Fair, circa 1993-1994 (Box 402, Folder 43)
    - International Fair / students / teacher in class, circa 1993-1994 (Box 402, Folder 44)
    - Student activities, circa 1993-1994 (Box 405, Folder 20)
    - Various sports / summer camp / student activities / exterior, 1994 (Box 402, Folder 45)
      Randy
    - Randy's photos, 1994 (Box 405, Folder 21)
    - Randy's photos - negatives, roll 1 of 3, 1994 (Box 402, Folder 46)
    - Randy's photos - negatives, roll 2 of 3, 1994 (Box 402, Folder 47)
    - Randy's photos - negatives, roll 3 of 3, 1994 (Box 402, Folder 48)
    - Yearbook layouts, Oversize, 1994 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - Yearbook Contact sheets – Group students, Candid, Arts, 1994 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Yearbook Contact sheets/negatives – Group students, 1994 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Flagstone repair / New Facility / Open chapel / Bookstore kids / book recycle, 1994 (Box 253, Folder 14)
    - Holiday Celebration / 2nd graders on steps / media panel, April, 1994 (Box 253, Folder 15)
    - Summer challenge, June, 1994 (Box 253, Folder 16)
    - SA / Petting Zoo, July, 1994 (Box 253, Folder 17)
    - RA Petting Zoo / Alumni luncheon, July, 1994 (Box 253, Folder 18)
    - Old St. Anne's Church / Packer head of school and others, September, 1994 (Box 253, Folder 19)
    - First day in the garden, September, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - Williams and Impollonia class room / Student Reading, September, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - Girls Soccer, October, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Scapino Cast / Students at work, October, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - B. Prosky / E. Wiesel Reprints, October, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Girls Volleyball / Founder's Day, November, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - Facing history and ourselves / Lower School Children in the library, October, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 7)
    - First grade opening, November, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 8)
    - Middle School Science & History Exhibit / Upper School candid photos / Lower School family portraits/ Middle School music students / Alumni room, November, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 9)
    - Summer's night dream / library scenes / student candids, November, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 10)
    - Winter Sing, December, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 11)
    - Winter Sing, December, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 12)
    - Choral concert/ Middle School candids / Great Bill Silletti, December, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn breakfast / Brass choir on tour / Music at Met Life, December, 1994 (Box 254, Folder 14)
    - Merit scholars / student candids, December, 1994 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - MPS, 1994 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Fencing team, 1994 (Box 526, Folder 24)
      Includes related correspondence, 2013
    - Unidentified man (President?), circa 1994 (Box 289, Folder 18)
    - A-1 Missing Prints, circa 1994 (Box 289, Folder 19)
    - B-1 Missing Prints, circa 1994 (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Framed basketball photograph with mat signed by students - Oversize, circa 1994 (Box 548, Folder -)
    - Jules Feiffer and fencing, January 1994 (Box 402, Folder 49)
    - Jules Feiffer / fencing team / boys basketball / #18, January 1994 (Box 402, Folder 50)
    - Boys basketball / skating party, January 1994 (Box 402, Folder 51)
    - Packer in the snow / cute girl and boy at work / #17, January 1994 (Box 402, Folder 52)
    - Packer in the snow / skating party, January 1994 (Box 402, Folder 53)
    - Trustee scholars / actors / Kids at Chemical / #19, January 1994 (Box 402, Folder 54)
    - Dance concert / basketball, February 1994 (Box 402, Folder 55)
    - Garden candids in the snow / Richard Bulet(?) / 100 day / Cornel(?) West, February 1994 (Box 402, Folder 56)
    - Faculty music and art festival / 12+ club / K. Rush, February 1994 (Box 402, Folder 57)
    - Health Advisory Committee / Iroquois village, February 1994 (Box 402, Folder 58)
    - International desserts / Egypt museum, March 1994 (Box 402, Folder 59)
    - Robert Leathers Design Day / Upper School course registration, March 1994 (Box 402, Folder 60)
    - Robert Leathers Design Day, March 1994 (Box 402, Folder 61)
    - Robert Leathers Design Day / Gymnastics B / #20, March 1994 (Box 402, Folder 62)
    - Scholastic Gold Key winners / garden candids, March 1994 (Box 402, Folder 63)
    - St. Denis chapel / career seminar / annual report #20, March 1994 (Box 402, Folder 64)
    - Lower School art opening / girls basketball, March 1994 (Box 402, Folder 65)
    - International Fair / Cum Laude party / CTY / Ellen (?) / #23, April 1994 (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - International Fair / Jim Henderson, April 1994 (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - International Fair / #24, April 1994 (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - cum laudes / art room / kids in garden / International Fair, April 1994 (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Gymnastics B, May 1994 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Baylin-Babbott / 5th and 6th grade math fair / Eclipse nice B. Moore and Vanessa Palazio, May 1994 (Box 403, Folder 6)
    - Gymnastics B, May 1994 (Box 403, Folder 7)
    - May dancing, May 1994 (Box 403, Folder 8)
    - 7th grade trip / annual giving thank-you party / Trustee visiting day / Rebecca's gymnastics / #22, May 1994 (Box 403, Folder 9)
    - May dancing, May 1994 (Box 403, Folder 10)
    - J. Langton / Packer Brass at Shea, May 1994 (Box 403, Folder 11)
    - New alumni lunch / Dutch Day, June 1994 (Box 403, Folder 12)
    - Jazz band / Moving up Day / 5th grade Sparta-Athens / Lisa Bordoff / Williams and Reiss befores / #25, June 1994 (Box 403, Folder 13)
    - Women's Sports Foundation, October 1994 (Box 403, Folder 14)
    - Soccer, November 1994 (Box 403, Folder 15)
    - Students - contact sheets, 1994-1995 (Box 526, Folder 25)
    - Chapel Tiffany Windows, 1995 (Box 304, Folder 49)
    - Garden construction, 1995 (Box 304, Folder 26)
    - International Fair and Playground, 1995 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 1995 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous negatives and photos, 1995 (Box 290, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous photos, 1995 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous photos, 1995 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - Yearbook Negatives – Individual faculty, 1995 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Yearbook Photographs – Students, sports, 1995 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Yearbook Photographs – Students, Arts, 1995 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Yearbook Photographs – Individual Students, 1995 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Yearbook Photographs – Group students, 1995 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Yearbook layouts, Oversize, 1995 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - Geography Bee / Basketball / student candids, January, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Girls Basketball, January, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - Basketball, January, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - Garden candids / Preschool candid, January, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - Garden prospect / Basketball, January, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Bobbi Abrams, March, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 7)
    - Egyptian museum / Cassie Pare / Revolutionary soldiers / trustee scholars / busk / bobcat / merit finalists / Jimmy's Sidewalk, March, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 8)
    - Garden construction / underexposed / Scholastic winners, March, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 9)
    - Gymnastics championship, March, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 10)
    - General Hospital wedding, Spring, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 11)
    - Summer camp photos (no negatives), 1995 (Box 255, Folder 12)
    - Unknown, set (no negatives), 1995 (Box 255, Folder 13)
    - Upper School kids summer challenge / Farewell luncheon, July, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 14)
    - Back to school, September, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 15)
    - CS art students / Ellen Rosenweig / West/CT Luncheon, October, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 16)
    - Dance / Pumpkin patch, October, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - KGN Spirit masks / Pumpkin patch, October, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - William's spirit masks, October, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Pumpkin patch, October, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Pumpkin patch, October, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Soccer / Shakespeare in the chapel, October, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Brass choir in chapel / NASP commended, November, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Hal Wicke Judo, December, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - Spirits masks / ornaments / new trustees, December, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - Christmas stockings / Lincoln center tree lighting, December, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - 5th grade / senior citizens angel program, December, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 11)
    - Met Life / Buster Keaton, December, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 12)
    - J. Dolan's baby shower / Faculty candids, December, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 13)
    - Winter Sing / dance class, December, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 14)
    - Packer Challenge, Summer, 1995 (Box 256, Folder 15)
    - Talent show / textbook exchange, Summer, 1995 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous sports photographs, 1995 (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Fourth grade international affair, 1995 (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - '95 Graduation Contacts, 1995 (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Fasano with last kindergarten class, 1995 (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Model congress; Bookfair, 1995 (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous negatives, circa 1995 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Birthday card, blank, circa 1995 (Box 290, Folder 14)
    - Theatrical performance / students and parents in classroom, circa 1995 (Box 403, Folder 16)
    - Garden event, circa 1995 (Box 403, Folder 17)
    - International Fair / theatrical performance, circa 1995 (Box 403, Folder 18)
    - Baseball game at Keyspan Park, circa 1995 (Box 403, Folder 19)
    - Multi-school Model Congress / baseball team, circa 1995 (Box 403, Folder 20)
    - Pumpkin Patch / Packer building exterior / Miscellaneous / young students, circa 1995 (Box 403, Folder 21)
    - Musical performance, January 1995 (Box 403, Folder 22)
    - School activities, February 1995 (Box 403, Folder 23)
    - "Campaign for Packer" kickoff party, February 1995 (Box 405, Folder 22)
    - Parent Association garden project, April 1995 (Box 405, Folder 23)
    - Parent Association garden project, April 1995 (Box 403, Folder 24)
      Some photos have stickers on reverse side, which has damaged following photos.
    - Playground and garden repair, April 1995 (Box 403, Folder 25)
    - Garden with 150th anniversary flag, 1996 (Box 304, Folder 17)
    - Yearbook layouts, Oversize, 1996 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - Yearbook layouts, Oversize, 1996 (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Yearbook layouts, Oversize, 1996 (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - Barbara Seddon, May, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 10)
    - David Reiss, May, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 11)
    - Ruth Browne / International Fair, May, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 12)
    - Old Timers, May, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 13)
    - Katie Maison / Packer Sander, May, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 14)
    - Philip Levine / Cum Laudes / Poster, May, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 15)
    - Color. AYSO Soccer & Chorus, May, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous slides, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 19)
    - M. Yatrakis School Candids, January, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 20)
    - Hal Wicke Judo, February, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 21)
    - 2nd Grade Ach. Project / Geography Bee, February, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Holiday Celebration / Computer Update / Girls 5th & 6th Grade Basketball, February, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - RM Architectural Contacts, February, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Film Crew / Women's Ensemble Gymnastics, March, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Old Timers / Chez Poker, March, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Film Crew / Packer Snow / Heather Flonescue with 3rd Graders, March, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - National Geography Bee / Packer Garden / Beijing Opera Co., March, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Peking Opera and International Studies, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - Scholastic Art & Writing / Award Winners, March, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 9)
    - Stage Combat Class, March, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 10)
    - Samels Foreign Language class / Cancer seminar, March, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Yatrakis / Basketball, April, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 12)
    - Yatrakis / Basketball, April, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 13)
    - R. Nisselson / Maria Yat and Peter Kelly, April, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 14)
    - Arts and PA Program at Packer, Paula Laverty April, 1996 (Box 258, Folder 15)
    - Events – Alumni Luncheon/Reunion, 1996 (Box 298, Folder 9)
    - Students in classes, 1996 (Box 406, Folder 44)
    - Camp Rich, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 26)
    - 96-002 Building front / garden facade, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 27)
    - "The Miser" theatrical performance, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 28)
    - 96-003 Opening of school / new faculty / artsy building shots, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 29)
    - 96-006 Students in garden and classroom, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 30)
    - 96-007 Susan Feibelman / Lower School kids in garden / Packer Trustees, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 31)
    - 96-007 Board of Trustees, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 24)
    - 96-008 Photos used in Viewbook / Music, sports, building exterior, academics, students in garden, 1996 (Box 406, Folder 43)
    - 96-010, 96-011 / Theater - "Don't Drink the Water", 1996 (Box 403, Folder 32)
    - 96-012 National Geographic Geography Bee / Raku Coryne, Meredith Moore, Victoria Restler, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 33)
      includes names and grades of students in Geography Bee photos
    - 96-013 Halloween party at Hope Project (from B. Coaney's slides), George Jones, 1996 (Box 405, Folder 25)
    - 96-015 Mary Stanton pajama breakfast / Guilt Pauth(?), J. Houston, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 34)
    - 96-022 Middle School Geography Bee, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 35)
    - 96-026 Preschool / Some 5th grade, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 36)
    - 96-027 5th Grade etiquette dinner, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 37)
    - 96-028 Seniors at Lavern's / D. Rutherford, A. Maddl, B. Cooney, R. Siegel, Reiss / Lower School in garden, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 38)
    - 96-029 7th Grade / C. Copeland / Dutch Day, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 39)
    - 96-030 Cross Country in Prospect Park, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 40)
    - 96-033 Alumni luncheon, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 41)
      Marc Hermann
    - 96-034 Graduation, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 42)
    - Student activities / Halloween, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 43)
    - Students / 124/10, 1996 (Box 403, Folder 44)
    - Maypole I and II, circa 1996 (Box 403, Folder 45)
      Marc A. Hermann
    - Student luncheon?, circa 1996 (Box 403, Folder 46)
    - 96-017 Senior breakfast in Alumni Room, February 1996 (Box 403, Folder 47)
    - 96-005 Pippin - young alumni event, May 1996 (Box 403, Folder 48)
    - 96-020 May Day dancing, May 1996 (Box 403, Folder 49)
    - 96-001 Suffolk luncheon / day camp kids, July 1996 (Box 403, Folder 50)
    - 96-007 Pumpkin Patch, October 1996 (Box 403, Folder 51)
    - Index to 1996-1997 photographs (Box 406, Folder 45)
    - Yearbook layouts, Oversize, 1996-1997 (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - Yearbook Photographs – Class photos, 1996-1997 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - Student activities, including graduation, circa 1996-1997 (Box 405, Folder 26)
    - Yearbook Photographs – Group Faculty Shots, 1997 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - 96-014 Randy's Visit, December 2, 1997 (Box 258, Folder 16)
    - 96-018 Randy's Visit, May 6, 1997 (Box 258, Folder 17)
    - 96-025 Luncheon by Kirvin Maule, 1997 (Box 258, Folder 18)
    - 96-031 Graduation 1997 Luncheon by Kirvin Maule (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - 97-001 New Faculty, 1997 (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - 97-002 New Faculty, J. DeVeau-Rosen, C. Guarero, R. Traub, 1997 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - 97-003 Bob Bey firestarting Middle School in garden, 1997 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - 97-004 Randy Matusow, October 29, 1997 (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - 97-005 Randy Matusow, October 29, 1997 (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - 97-006 "The Personals", 1997 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - 97-007 "The Orphan Train", 1997 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - 97-008 "The Orphan Train", 1997 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - 97-009 Tree Planting Seniors at Lauren's, November, 1997 (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - 97-010 Inyer's Science and Joyce H's Snails, 1997 (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - 97-011 Maria Adams' Photos of Lower School Winter Sing, 1997 (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - 97-012 "The Personals", 1997 (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - 97-026 4th Grade International Fair, 1997 (Box 260, Folder 12)
    - 97-028 Maypole, 1997 (Box 260, Folder 14)
    - 97-029 "Once Upon a Mattress", 1997 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - 97-030 "Once Upon a Mattress" L. Berry, 1997 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - 97-031 Parent Association Book Fair, 1997 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - 97-032a Faculty Portraits, 1997 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - 97-033 Porfman /Basketball / Faculty Portraits, 1997 (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - 97-034 Faculty Portraits / Basketball Trip II, 1997 (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - With Film Canister, March 29, 1997 (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - Summer camp, 1997 (Box 403, Folder 52)
    - Theater / students at play in garden, circa 1997 (Box 403, Folder 53)
    - 96-014, February 1997 (Box 405, Folder 27)
    - 96-016 Upper School chorus Vienna benefit concert, March 1997 (Box 403, Folder 54)
    - 96-023 Theater - "Crazy for You" roll 1, May 1997 (Box 403, Folder 55)
    - 96-019 Theater - "Crazy for You" roll 2 / May Day dancing, May 1997 (Box 403, Folder 56)
    - 96-024 Emily Berry's Packer Model / "Crazy for You" alumni party, May 1997 (Box 403, Folder 57)
    - 96-021 Garden scenes / chapel glass / "Crazy for You", May 1997 (Box 403, Folder 58)
    - 96-032 Class of 1997 on school steps, June 1997 (Box 403, Folder 59)
    - Unidentified ceremony / children playing in garden, June 1997 (Box 403, Folder 60)
    - Children playing in garden, June 1997 (Box 403, Folder 61)
    - Sports award ceremony, July 1997 (Box 403, Folder 62)
    - 97-013 "The Orphan Train" reprints (Middle School Fall Play), 1998 (Box 259, Folder 14)
    - 97-014 PCI by Randy, 1998 (Box 259, Folder 15)
    - 97-015 Career Day, 1998 (Box 259, Folder 16)
    - 97-016A Randy M's Visit, March 11, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - 97-016B Babbott / Middle School / Greek tragedies, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - 97-017 Barbara Brick's chess pictures, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - 97-018 Middle School Play "Twelfth Night" (1/2), 1998 (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - 97-019 Middle School Play "Twelfth Night" (2/2), 1998 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - 97-020 Alumni Board At Lauren's Garden, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - 97-021 Ben Dorfman on Brooklyn Bridge, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - 97-022 Jazz Ensemble in Fifth Floor Art Studio, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - 97-023 Boys Basketball at Red Hook, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - 97-024 Varsity Volleyball & Boy's Baseball, April 24, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - 97-025 Luncheon taken by Randy M, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 11)
    - 97-027 Lower School Garden Dancing, May 15, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 13)
    - 97-032b Pratt Theater Opening, January 27 / Randy Matusow Negatives, 1999 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - 97-035A Fifth Grade Etiquette Dinner (K D'Attolo), 1997 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - 97-035B Graduation 1998, R. Matusow (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - 98-001 Suffolk Luncheon / Theater construction, 1998 (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - 98-003 S. O'Shea / Student Independent Study, June, 1998 (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - 98-004 Old Coach in Alumni Room / Theater Construction, September 3, 1998 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - 98-005 New Faculty David Ruiz / "Welcome Back" breakfast / Theater construction, September, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - 98-006 Senior Lock-In, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - 98-007 Opening Chapel, National Merit Students, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - 98-008A Slides, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - 98-008B Prints from slides, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - 98-009 Theater Construction / Lower School in Garden Lunch Room, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - 98-010 Soccer in Red Hook / DA Quilt Bob Berg / Church Interior, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - 98-010 Summer Camp '98 taken by Jacque, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - 98-011 Soccer in Red Hook, October 5, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - 98-012 MSILS Together / Theater construction October, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - 98-013 7th Grade Camping Trip, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - 98-014 National Merit Students / George Boutis, 1998 (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - 98-015 Jim Short / Biology AP / "Romeo & Juliet" (1 of 5), 1998 (Box 262, Folder 13)
    - 98-016 "Romeo and Juliet" (2 of 5), 1998 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - 98-017 "Romeo & Juliet" (3 of 5), 1998 (Box 262, Folder 15)
    - 98-018 "Romeo & Juliet" (4 of 5), 1998 (Box 262, Folder 16)
    - 98-019 "Romeo & Juliet" (5 of 5), 1998 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - 98-020 2nd Grade Yoga / Theater Construction, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - 98-021 Main Library / Sabrina Martin / Frances Jule Library, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - 98-022 Randy Duchain Visit, November 11, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - 98-023 Guys & Dolls I, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - 98-024 Guys & Dolls II, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - 98-025 Guys & Dolls III, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - 98-026 Late November / B. Dorfman & United Nations, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - 98-027 Theater Construction, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - 98-028A Theater Last Stage / Lower School Comp Opening, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - 98-028B Lower School Winter Sing, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 11)
    - 98-029 Career Day, February 5, 1999 (Box 263, Folder 12)
    - 98-030 Career Day, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 13)
    - 98-031 Dance Concert, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - 98-032 George Oelmhorst's Photos of Pratt / Theater Opening, 1998 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - 98-033 Summer Camp Photos, 1998 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - 98-034 Pratt Theater / M. Lang, 1998 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - 98-035 Pratt Theater Festival, 1998 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - 98-036 Fresh Hearts / Brooklyn Museum, 1998 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - 98-037 Brooklyn Museum / Fresh Hearts, 1998 (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - 98-038 Story Theater (1 of 4), 1998 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - 98-039 Story Theater (2 of 4), 1998 (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - 98-044 Alumni Luncheon, May 5, 1999 (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - 98-048 Randy Matusow, May Day, May 14, 1999 (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - 98-052 Graduation, Randy Matusow, 1999 (Box 264, Folder 11)
    - Story Theater (3 of 4), 1998 (Box 264, Folder 12)
    - Story Theater (4 of 4), 1998 (Box 264, Folder 13)
    - Baggage For Trip, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - 4th Grade / International Fair, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Book Fair, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Middle School Baseball, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - May Day Dancing, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - 8th Grade Fulton Ferry, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - 5th Grade Health Dinner, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Prospect Hall / Park Slope, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - May Pole, July, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Theater Photos, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Holiday Card Photos, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - Negatives in Paper Sleeves, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - Yearbook Photographs – Class Photos, 1998 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - Packer Campus - Oversize, 1999 (Box 540, Folder -)
    - 99-001 Brenda's shower / Hidden door / Opening chapel / new Faculty / Anya Raab, 1999 (Box 265, Folder 13)
    - 99-002 Anya Raab at Charles Hynes / Boys and Girls soccer, 1999 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - 99-003 Boys Soccer, 1999 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - 99-004A Biran Kosnik, George Snook / Fenestrations at Grand Central, 1999 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - 99-004B Barabra Brick / Packer DLUS, 1999 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - 99-005 Pumpkin Patch on Sunday, 1999 (Box 266, Folder 5)